export const quiz = {
  topic: 'Javascript',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 4,
  perQuestionScore: 5,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What is the meaning of "गुरु" in English?',
      choices: ['Friend', 'Teacher', 'Man', 'Son'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: 'In which language does "नमस्ते" mean "hello"?',
      choices: ['Hindi', 'Sanskrit', 'Marathi', 'Tamil'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the meaning of the word "विद्या"?',
      choices: ['Play', 'Book', 'Knowledge', 'Music'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: 'What is another name for "गजः"?',
      choices: ['Monkey', 'Bull', 'Deer', 'Elephant'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: 'To whom does "अर्जुनः" refer?',
      choices: ['Rama', 'Krishna', 'Yudhishthira', 'Bhima'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the meaning of the word "सुन्दर"?',
      choices: ['Cruel', 'Beloved', 'Happy', 'Beautiful'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the suffix of the word "मातृ"?',
      choices: ['तृ', 'तृत्व', 'तृण्', 'मा'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "प्रज्ञा" mean?',
      choices: ['Wisdom', 'Punishment', 'Thought', 'Soul'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'What is another name for "आकाश"?',
      choices: ['Earth', 'Water', 'Air', 'Sky'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the opposite of "अद्भुत"?',
      choices: ['Beautiful', 'Unique', 'Terrible', 'Ordinary'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 4,
    },
  ],
}